const math = [
  {
    question: "59 + 95",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 154,
    wrong_answers: [54, 102, 112],
  },
  {
    question: "313 x 5",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 1565,
    wrong_answers: [1315, 1535, 1554],
  },
  {
    question: "376 - 1",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 375,
    wrong_answers: [275, 323, 333],
  },
  {
    question: "304 x 79",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 24016,
    wrong_answers: [23766, 23986, 24005],
  },
  {
    question: "116 - 79",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 37,
    wrong_answers: [36, 32, -13],
  },
  {
    question: "364 - 27",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 337,
    wrong_answers: [237, 285, 295],
  },
  {
    question: "167 + 65",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 232,
    wrong_answers: [132, 180, 190],
  },
  {
    question: "42 - 49",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: -7,
    wrong_answers: [-8, -12, -57],
  },
  {
    question: "383 + 39",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 422,
    wrong_answers: [322, 370, 380],
  },
  {
    question: "72 x 67",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 4824,
    wrong_answers: [4574, 4794, 4813],
  },
  {
    question: "171 - 21",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 150,
    wrong_answers: [50, 98, 108],
  },
  {
    question: "52 - 25",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 27,
    wrong_answers: [26, 22, -23],
  },
  {
    question: "229 - 37",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 192,
    wrong_answers: [92, 140, 150],
  },
  {
    question: "5 - 87",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: -82,
    wrong_answers: [-83, -87, -132],
  },
  {
    question: "61 x 1",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 61,
    wrong_answers: [60, 56, 11],
  },
  {
    question: "177 + 5",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 182,
    wrong_answers: [82, 130, 140],
  },
  {
    question: "120 - 83",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 37,
    wrong_answers: [36, 32, -13],
  },
  {
    question: "273 - 81",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 192,
    wrong_answers: [92, 140, 150],
  },
  {
    question: "275 x 25",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 6875,
    wrong_answers: [6625, 6845, 6864],
  },
  {
    question: "62 x 31",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 1922,
    wrong_answers: [1672, 1892, 1911],
  },
  {
    question: "386 x 11",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 4246,
    wrong_answers: [3996, 4216, 4235],
  },
  {
    question: "179 x 77",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 13783,
    wrong_answers: [13533, 13753, 13772],
  },
  {
    question: "25 + 97",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 122,
    wrong_answers: [121, 117, 72],
  },
  {
    question: "341 - 87",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 254,
    wrong_answers: [154, 202, 212],
  },
  {
    question: "190 x 13",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 2470,
    wrong_answers: [2220, 2440, 2459],
  },
  {
    question: "361 - 43",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 318,
    wrong_answers: [218, 266, 276],
  },
  {
    question: "121 x 83",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 10043,
    wrong_answers: [9793, 10013, 10032],
  },
  {
    question: "235 - 25",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 210,
    wrong_answers: [110, 158, 168],
  },
  {
    question: "35 x 29",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 1015,
    wrong_answers: [765, 985, 1004],
  },
  {
    question: "356 - 85",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 271,
    wrong_answers: [171, 219, 229],
  },
  {
    question: "25 + 5",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 30,
    wrong_answers: [29, 25, -20],
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 51",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 357,
    wrong_answers: [257, 305, 315],
  },
  {
    question: "202 x 25",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 5050,
    wrong_answers: [4800, 5020, 5039],
  },
  {
    question: "269 + 85",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 354,
    wrong_answers: [254, 302, 312],
  },
  {
    question: "337 - 79",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 258,
    wrong_answers: [158, 206, 216],
  },
  {
    question: "90 x 93",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 8370,
    wrong_answers: [8120, 8340, 8359],
  },
  {
    question: "371 x 85",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 31535,
    wrong_answers: [31285, 31505, 31524],
  },
  {
    question: "43 x 93",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 3999,
    wrong_answers: [3749, 3969, 3988],
  },
  {
    question: "34 + 57",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 91,
    wrong_answers: [90, 86, 41],
  },
  {
    question: "164 - 63",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 101,
    wrong_answers: [100, 96, 51],
  },
  {
    question: "397 x 77",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 30569,
    wrong_answers: [30319, 30539, 30558],
  },
  {
    question: "300 - 61",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 239,
    wrong_answers: [139, 187, 197],
  },
  {
    question: "33 - 93",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: -60,
    wrong_answers: [-61, -65, -110],
  },
  {
    question: "272 + 29",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 301,
    wrong_answers: [201, 249, 259],
  },
  {
    question: "85 x 3",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 255,
    wrong_answers: [155, 203, 213],
  },
  {
    question: "229 - 53",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 176,
    wrong_answers: [76, 124, 134],
  },
  {
    question: "67 - 7",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 60,
    wrong_answers: [59, 55, 10],
  },
  {
    question: "153 + 9",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 162,
    wrong_answers: [62, 110, 120],
  },
  {
    question: "116 x 59",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 6844,
    wrong_answers: [6594, 6814, 6833],
  },
  {
    question: "368 + 3",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 371,
    wrong_answers: [271, 319, 329],
  },
  {
    question: "281 + 55",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 336,
    wrong_answers: [236, 284, 294],
  },
  {
    question: "201 + 25",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 226,
    wrong_answers: [126, 174, 184],
  },
  {
    question: "390 + 95",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 485,
    wrong_answers: [385, 433, 443],
  },
  {
    question: "173 + 79",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 252,
    wrong_answers: [152, 200, 210],
  },
  {
    question: "306 - 69",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 237,
    wrong_answers: [137, 185, 195],
  },
  {
    question: "302 + 35",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 337,
    wrong_answers: [237, 285, 295],
  },
  {
    question: "123 - 3",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 120,
    wrong_answers: [119, 115, 70],
  },
  {
    question: "251 - 21",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 230,
    wrong_answers: [130, 178, 188],
  },
  {
    question: "198 + 77",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 275,
    wrong_answers: [175, 223, 233],
  },
  {
    question: "300 x 67",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 20100,
    wrong_answers: [19850, 20070, 20089],
  },
  {
    question: "254 - 41",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 213,
    wrong_answers: [113, 161, 171],
  },
  {
    question: "182 + 99",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 281,
    wrong_answers: [181, 229, 239],
  },
  {
    question: "212 + 3",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 215,
    wrong_answers: [115, 163, 173],
  },
  {
    question: "142 + 57",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 199,
    wrong_answers: [99, 147, 157],
  },
  {
    question: "104 - 97",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 7,
    wrong_answers: [6, 2, -43],
  },
  {
    question: "246 - 45",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 201,
    wrong_answers: [101, 149, 159],
  },
  {
    question: "246 + 15",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 261,
    wrong_answers: [161, 209, 219],
  },
  {
    question: "79 x 91",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 7189,
    wrong_answers: [6939, 7159, 7178],
  },
  {
    question: "312 + 69",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 381,
    wrong_answers: [281, 329, 339],
  },
  {
    question: "304 + 69",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 373,
    wrong_answers: [273, 321, 331],
  },
  {
    question: "188 x 39",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 7332,
    wrong_answers: [7082, 7302, 7321],
  },
  {
    question: "48 + 97",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 145,
    wrong_answers: [144, 140, 95],
  },
  {
    question: "307 x 29",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 8903,
    wrong_answers: [8653, 8873, 8892],
  },
  {
    question: "174 + 93",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 267,
    wrong_answers: [167, 215, 225],
  },
  {
    question: "363 x 27",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 9801,
    wrong_answers: [9551, 9771, 9790],
  },
  {
    question: "83 + 53",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 136,
    wrong_answers: [135, 131, 86],
  },
  {
    question: "57 x 75",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 4275,
    wrong_answers: [4025, 4245, 4264],
  },
  {
    question: "33 - 57",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: -24,
    wrong_answers: [-25, -29, -74],
  },
  {
    question: "69 + 25",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 94,
    wrong_answers: [93, 89, 44],
  },
  {
    question: "254 + 13",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 267,
    wrong_answers: [167, 215, 225],
  },
  {
    question: "45 + 19",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 64,
    wrong_answers: [63, 59, 14],
  },
  {
    question: "347 - 57",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 290,
    wrong_answers: [190, 238, 248],
  },
  {
    question: "136 x 17",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 2312,
    wrong_answers: [2062, 2282, 2301],
  },
  {
    question: "104 x 79",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 8216,
    wrong_answers: [7966, 8186, 8205],
  },
  {
    question: "111 - 85",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 26,
    wrong_answers: [25, 21, -24],
  },
  {
    question: "340 x 71",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 24140,
    wrong_answers: [23890, 24110, 24129],
  },
  {
    question: "223 + 9",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 232,
    wrong_answers: [132, 180, 190],
  },
  {
    question: "335 + 19",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 354,
    wrong_answers: [254, 302, 312],
  },
  {
    question: "225 - 33",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 192,
    wrong_answers: [92, 140, 150],
  },
  {
    question: "331 - 33",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 298,
    wrong_answers: [198, 246, 256],
  },
  {
    question: "325 - 1",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 324,
    wrong_answers: [224, 272, 282],
  },
  {
    question: "329 - 45",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 284,
    wrong_answers: [184, 232, 242],
  },
  {
    question: "343 + 75",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 418,
    wrong_answers: [318, 366, 376],
  },
  {
    question: "264 - 55",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 209,
    wrong_answers: [109, 157, 167],
  },
  {
    question: "26 + 53",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 79,
    wrong_answers: [78, 74, 29],
  },
  {
    question: "102 - 13",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 89,
    wrong_answers: [88, 84, 39],
  },
  {
    question: "200 - 45",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 155,
    wrong_answers: [55, 103, 113],
  },
  {
    question: "396 x 63",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 24948,
    wrong_answers: [24698, 24918, 24937],
  },
  {
    question: "85 - 17",
    level: "EASY",
    answer: 68,
    wrong_answers: [67, 63, 18],
  },
  {
    question: "160 x 89",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 14240,
    wrong_answers: [13990, 14210, 14229],
  },
  {
    question: "332 + 51",
    level: "MEDIUM",
    answer: 383,
    wrong_answers: [283, 331, 341],
  },
  {
    question: "265 x 71",
    level: "HARD",
    answer: 18815,
    wrong_answers: [18565, 18785, 18804],
  },
];

export default math;
